Hi.
I'm so glad that you are here.
Welcome to my course, complete Linux training course to get your dream I.T. job.
Let me put in a very simple words.
When you take my course at the end of this course, you're going to learn so many things about Linux
that you will be able to apply for a Linux job and you will get the job.
Fair enough.
My name is Imron Afsal and I've been in I.T. for almost a decade and a half.
I've been working in New York City for financial firm and tech media industries.
I've been teaching for a while now.
And the biggest thing and the best thing about my teaching is every time I teach, I make sure the person
who is taking my course will get the job at the end of my course.
So are you ready to take this journey with me?